Alright.
Most guys put a little bit of hockey tape on there for you.
Everybody's got their own style.
I like to....I mean pretty much your just getting a better grip with the tape on there and you don't want to lose the stick.
I do a little twist here like this.
It kind of forms to your fingers...and just work it back up.
Some guys will go a little bit farther down, it's just personal preference.
I mean, it's not that big a deal really.
Just work your way up though.
When I get to the top I like to make a nice little knob here...wrap it around a couple more times.
Make a knob there just so the stick won?t come out of my hand.
And there you go.
Just a nice little tape job just as big as my hand.